

September 8, 2017

Krista Krebs 3014 Estate Drive Oakdale, PA 15071 412-915-8823

Adobe Creative Cloud Experience Designer 601 Townsend St

San Francisco, CA 94103

Dear Adobe Creative Cloud team,

I am excited to write today to apply for the Experience Designer position. With a degree in Product Design & Development from Penn State, I believe I am a great fit for the Experience Designer role because of my experience collaborating with multiple stakeholders to not only design intuitive interfaces, but also develop them. Having engineering experience gives me an edge, to think of design as a system, not just for how it looks, but how it works.

Currently at DICK'S Sporting Goods, I am Lead Mobile UI/UX Designer and Lead Android Developer. These positions have given me the opportunity to wear many hats, and understand not only technical opportunities and constraints, but the importance of understanding the user's goals. My collective experiences - design through development- have presented me the right type of circumstances to grasp the entire software development lifecycle. I have an influence in every step from gathering requirements, to user research and interviews, to synthesizing data, to design sprinting, to testing with users, to handing the design specs over to developers, and ultimately, bringing the vision to life through development. This also makes me a great team member because I have empathy for each role, and how each's individual goals are all equally important in contributing to the team's overarching success.

Enclosed is my resume that describes my experience, skills, and education in more detail, as well as where you can find me on the web! Please also check out my portfolio website (http://krista.design), where you can browse other personal projects that are in addition to my work experience listed in my resume.

I believe I can be an asset to the team and look forward to hearing more about this opportunity and how I can help the Adobe Creative Cloud team continue to make products that empower creatives like myself!

Kind regards, Krista



Contact

- http://krista.design
- (412)-915-8823
- krista@krista.design
- http://mangopair.com
- dribbble.com/
 KristaKrebs
- in linkedin.com/in/ kristakrebs
- (a) @Krista.Design
- **●** @KristaKrebs

Skills

Design:

User Journeys & Flows, Personas, Design Sprints, Customer Research through Interviews/Surveys, Use Case Scenarios, Wireframes, Visual Mockups

Photoshop, Sketch, Illustrator, Zeplin, InVision, Marvel, Keynote, proto.io, Wacom Tablet

Code:

Java (Android)

JSON, Git, HTML, CSS

Swift (iOS) XML, JS, SQL, PHP

People:

Leadership, Teamwork, Communication, Emotional Intelligence

Krista Krebs

Product Designer, Mobile App Engineer

Work Experience

Mobile App Engineer, UI/UX Designer

May 2015-Present

DICK'S Sporting Goods

Coraopolis, PA

- -In an agile process, develop features in the DSG Consumer Mobile Application as Lead Android Developer including CRM Integration, Fitness Tracker Integration (MOVE), Gift Cards, Store Finder, and more.
- -Design UI/UX deliverables to meet customer needs by working with product management, customer service, and customers to understand business requirements, feedback, & pain points.
- -Work diligently managing developers and QA overseeing code reviews and test case preparation to ensure high quality delivery.
- -Communicate with multiple vendors to oversee customer research strategy, gather technical requirements, and ultimately implement solutions.

UX Designer (Freelancer)

May 2016-Sept 2016

SignEasy

San Francisco, CA (Remote)

- -Audited iOS & Android applications in a complete UI/UX Review to determine direction for their product roadmap.
- -Designed user personas, journeys & flows, use case scenarios, and wireframes for Request Signature, to deliver the product team's vision.

Developer, Project Manager

May 2013/14-Aug 2013/14

The Boeing Company

Ridley Park, PA & Charleston, SC

- -Designed over 14 data flows to facilitate knowledge transfer of information systems and developed 113 stored procedures to contribute to a rewrite of an enterprise wide application.
- -Designed and managed development of a Human Resources web application prototype incorporating the user centered design process.

Education

Penn State University, University Park

2010-2015

B.S. Product Design & Development in Information Sciences & Tech Minor in Film Studies

Student Marshall for Graduating Class of December 2015 Cumulative GPA: **3.99**, Major GPA: **4.0**